So hello everyone welcome back to your own
video in this video we will discuss
about the quarter one financial results of ICI Lord General Insurance Company
so first here our company has disclosed its
quarter one financial results
let's see
how the results were we will check it fundamentally
and also do its technical analysis we will
also look at future support targets
so the video is going to be very important
before that if you are new to the channel then please
subscribe to the channel and turn on the bell icon
so that you can get this time's latest video on
time this is my request to you
this motivation is given to me so please
support let's start the video so first of all let's
talk about the sales of this company so where last
year the sales of the company were 4716 crores there is a
great jump of 19%
and this time the sales have come to 5601 crores on year on year
basis there is a jump of %
which was last year's sales
5391 crore, so
if seen on quarter to quarter basis, then there is a jump of
almost 3.8% in the sales of the company on quarter to quarter
basis and year to year basis.
Talking about the net profits front, where last year the
net profit of the company was 390 crores, there has been a
great jump of 49%, so we
can say that this time profit of 580 crores has been
seen and on
quarter to quarter basis it has also increased from 520 to
580, which if seen percentage wise, then
its
profits have been seen to increase by 17.3% on
cut-off basis. On the other hand, there is a
jump of 48% in their profit on cut-off basis.
Talking about EPS, there has been an
increase of 48% this time and it has come to
1177% which was 7.95% last year, if we
talk about it then the profit has also increased to 51%.  Growth has been seen
this time, the profit has increased from Rs 510 crore to Rs
770 crore. The
quarter one results of this ICI Lord company were quite impressive. A
very solid jump was seen on
both cut basis and no basis. It is good to
see on all fronts, whether it is net
profit, EPS, sales, the stock performed well in all. The
stock has generated solid profits.
It has also benefited the market
estimators a lot. Let us now see
how you are getting to see on a technical basis. So
we have
opened the weekly time chart of the stock. If you look at the setup of the chart, if we
talk about September
2021, then the stock
faced a resistance there and a continuous
decline was seen here, a
pattern of lower higher lows i.e. lower lows was seen forming.
Coming to this level and
reaching the level of 1100, the stock formed a double bottom
and from here the stock
broke it and continued moving
in the direction of upward move. You will see the stock for the
last some time, for the last few quarter
weeks  So, we are seeing some very large
candles. If we
show you, if we talk about showing it here, then
this was also formed in January, a good candle.
Then again, if we talk about weeks, then in the
last 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, or the last
seven weeks, if you look at it, the
stock has never breached its lower level. By
continuously forming a pattern of highs and lows, the
stock had
reached trading near 1900 at the current time and from there, the
stock is currently
trading around 18811. If we look at the performance of the last year, the
stock has given investors a jump
profit of 38%. This stock has given a return of 38%. If
we examine this stock once on the daily
time frame, then its setup, which is
continuously forming a pattern of highs and lows, is
always moving in the upward direction. It is
also creating a channel. This is
its channel. When it continuously
goes above this channel, it goes to the upper band and from
here it finds resistance.  And it
keeps going down. Then, when you take support on this channel, it's
ready for an up move. The
stock's results are quite impressive,
whether it's on a quarter-on-quarter basis
or a year-on-year basis.
I've found the results on both fronts to be
quite good. So, there's a good
positive sentiment in the stock. The stock
can show a good move in the coming times. Currently, the stock is
trading
around 881. If you analyze the volumes,
you've seen
good participation in volumes for the past few days.
Considering this,
if the stock breaks out of this channel,
if it breaks above 1900 and
sustains there, then the stock
could show levels up to 2200 in the coming times.
This is my point of view. What is yours?
Please let me
know by commenting in the comments section. So friends, how did you like this video?
If you liked it, please like the video and
subscribe to the channel. Turn on the bell icon
so you can be the first to receive this time's notification. Until then, see you next time.
Thank you for watching in the video